FANTAHUN FEKADU

Addis Ababa, Ethiopia | +251-938-646985 | fantahunefekadu1@gmail.com

https://linkedin.com/in/fantahun-fekadu

https://github.com/FANIMAN

Professional Summary

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering three years of related experience.

Skills

- React JS, Javascript
- HTML5, CSS3

- Node JS, Express JS
- Flutter, Golang, Python

Work History

Intern Flutter Developer

10/2021 to 12/2021

Side Hustle - Ibadan, Nigeria

- Develop a flutter app.
- Deployed flutter app to cloud infrastructures

Web Developer Intern

06/2021 to 10/2021

Ministry of Innovation and Technology (MINT) - Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

- Building React JS project.
- Designing user interface components for web apps.

Full Stack Web and Mobile App Developer (Freelace)

08/2019 - Present

Upwork Inc. - Virtual

- Worked on different Mobile and Web projects using different Programming Langauges.
- Designed, implemented and monitored API's using Node, Golang.
- Provided high level of assistance to customers regarding their projects.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering

Addis Ababa Institute of Technology: Class of 2021/22